<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ Multiverse: Blue Judge Options ]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[ https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/88/multiverse-blue-judge-options ]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Duodecimus ]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ MV5.5.1 v1.10 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[ 
This mod modifies the Node 17 judge event to turn options not yet shown to them blue.
Specifically, it removes the judge boon event and re-adds it.
Supports:
	Multiverse (5.5.1)
	Forgotten Diamonds (1.6.5)
	Forgotten Races (16.27)
	Forgemaster (0.6.1.2.2)
	Insurrection + Selection (5.5.1)
	C&C Weapons: Renegade (5.0)
	Fishier Than Light (1.2.3)
	Darkest Desire (4.0.2)
	The Outer Expansion (7.1.8)
	Lily's Innovations (1.6.2)
	Expanded Multiverse (0.6.1)
	Alder's Additions (2.1.1)

Any other mods that also modify boons will need to be loaded after this mod.
Let me know about them and I can add support!

This mod should be loaded after the supported mods, but before any unsupported boon adders.

EX:
Multiverse Assets/Data
Forgotten Races Assets/Data <=(supported)
Forgotten Races Diamonds <=(supported)
Judge Blue Options <=(This mod)
Some other boons mod <=(unsupported)



V1.1: Fixed Forgemaster's Modular Hull boon
V1.2: Fixed CnC's Nuclear Payload boon, Forgotten Diamonds Flesh Maker
V1.3: Fixed Forgotten Race's Haunt gun always being blue, fixed Forgemaster's Terminus, added Boon from Fishier Than Light, added Forgotten Races's Spherax
V1.4: Added Darkest Desires Deep one crew and weapon, and disparity weapon, updated Forgotten Race's Haunts into Revenants
V1.5: Updated Darkest Desires and Outer Expansion to add new races and system boons. Some judge events are missing text as the text is not in the source addon.	Thanks to Aleev for coding this update! 
V1.6: Updated Darkest Desires new races and weapon. Thanks again to Aleev for coding this update! 
V1.7: MV 5.5 lowered the maximum possible teleporter level, fixed the boon requirement to match
V1.8: Added boons from Lily's Innovations and Expanded Multiverse
	Thanks again to Aleev for coding this update! 
V1.9: Added Lily's Innovation's Targeting system, and four boons from Alder's Additions
V1.10: Added Annelid boon from IPS
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>